What's going on?
怎么了？
My eye is a little itchy.
我的眼睛有点痒
Mine too. Yeah.
我的也是
It's really red. You should go see my eye doctor.
你的眼睛好红喔 你应该去看我的眼科医生
I'm not gonna see your ex-boyfriend.
理查？我才不要 找你的前男友看眼睛
That's all I hear. Richard, Richard, Richard.
理查…一天到晚理查个没完
Since we've dated, I've said his name twice.
打从我们开始约会以后 我想我只提过两次他的名字
Okay. So Richard, Richard.
那好，理查、理查
It's not Richard. It's this new guy. He's good.
不是理查啦 我新找的眼科医生很棒
I'm sorry. I'm not going to an eye doctor.
抱歉，我不去看眼科医生
-Oh, God. Here we go. -What?
天啊，老毛病又犯了 什么？
Anytime anything comes close to touching her eye or anyone else's...
每次只要碰到眼睛这档事 她马上就...
...she, like, freaks out. Watch.
...避之唯恐不及 注意看
Ross, come on!
罗斯，你别闹了
I have a weird thing with my eye. Can we not talk about it?
好，我对我的眼睛有怪癖 麻烦别再讨论了，行吗？
好吧…
Hey,Rach. You know that great song? "Me, Myself and Eye."
瑞秋，还记得有首很棒的歌 我、我自己和… （“我”和“眼睛”同音）
Monica! Come on!
摩妮卡，别闹啦
All those in favor of getting lunch, say, "eye."
有没有人想吃午餐？ 有意愿的请说…
Ross! Stop it!
罗斯，拜托别闹了啦
How much did I love The King and Eye?
我有多喜欢“国王与我”？
Chandler!
钱德！
Me too, me too!
我也是…
Just stop it! That's enough!
够了，别玩了…
-You okay there, man? -Yeah. I got too excited.
你还好吧？ 对，我真的戳到了
The One with Joey's Big Break
本集播出：“眼病难医”
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
I gotta go. I'm taking Ben to the park.
先走了，我要带班去公园
-Give him a kiss for me. -All right. Bye.
帮我亲一下他 好，再见
Later.
再见…
I'm so sorry you got caught in the middle of that.
很抱歉让你们夹在中间尴尬
I didn't mean to be so out there, but I am furious with him.
我也不是故意这么夸张 但我真的很生他的气
Calm down?
别激动
I'm trying. Man, that guy can push my buttons!
我在克制 但一想到那个人我就有气
Why are you so mad?
你干嘛那么气他？
-I don't wanna talk about it. -lt seems like
我不想谈，好吗？ 只是…
You wanna be on my list too? Keep talking.
你想榜上有名就继续说啊
Has anyone seen my list, by the way?
对了，谁有看到我的黑名单？
No. What's it look like?
没看到，长什么样子？
-A piece of paper and it says, "Ross." -I see.
就是张纸，上头写了“罗斯”  了解
I just got off the phone with Estelle. Guess what?
我刚和艾斯黛讲完电话 你们猜怎么了？
I got the lead in a movie!!!
我要当电影主角了！
You got the lead in a movie? What's it about?
你要演电影主角，太厉害了 是什么电影？
It's called Shutterspeed. It's really cool.
片名是“极限速度”， 超酷的
I meet this girl in the subway and we fall in love in, like, a day.
我在地铁遇见一个女孩 一天之内坠入情网
And then she disappears. But I find out where she lives.
后来她消失无踪 但我找出了她住在哪里
This old lady answers the door. I say,"Where's Betsy?"
一个老太太出来开门 我问她“贝丝在哪里？”
And she says, "Betsy's been dead for 10 years."
她说“贝丝已经过世十年了”
Chilling!
好寒
The best part is,we're filming in the desert outside of Vegas.
最棒的部分是 拍片地点在赌城外的沙漠
-You know what that means. -I know.
兄弟，你知道那是啥意思 对，我知道
Road trip! We can rent a car. I have to be there by Tuesday.
开车杀过去，我们可以租车 我周二以前到那里就行了
Wait! My grandmother's dead.
等等，我祖母过世了
We can talk about that too,Phoebe.
菲比，我们也可以聊聊那件事
No, her cab.
不…我是说她的计程车
She probably won't be using it. Drive it to Las Vegas.
她八成用不到了 你们可以开去赌城
All right! Thanks!
好耶，菲比，谢了
What are we gonna do about my job?
等等… 那我的工作怎么办？
Not go.
别去了
Great! Road trip,baby!
好耶！棒！上路罗！
Is this okay?
你没意见吧？
Chandler, you don't have to ask for my permission.
钱德，你不用徵求我的允许…
You can go.
我让你去 谢谢
Rach, we'll be late for the eye doctor.
瑞秋，快点，我们看医生要迟到了
All right. Let's get this over with.
好啦，早去早解脱
Look what I did.
糟糕，我真是笨手笨脚的
I mean, look at this mess.
搞得一团乱
We're gonna probably have to clean this up.
我得先来清理一下
I mean, we're gonna have to reschedule!
看诊时间得要重约了
If you thought that this mess was gonna bother me, you are wrong!
若你认为这点脏乱就会影响我 那你就错了
All right, let's go, Blinky.
我们走吧，眨眼姑娘
钱德！
“中央咖啡馆”
Hey,Joey. What's up?
乔伊 你怎么了？
I can't decide which route to take to Vegas.
我无法决定走哪条路去赌城
You've traveled a lot, right?
你去过不少地方吧？
Yeah,I've been around.
对，见过世面
Which route should I take? The north or the south route?
那我该选哪一条？ 北线还是南线？
If you take the north route, there's a man with a beard of bees.
走北线途经伊利诺州 有个男人会用蜜蜂当胡子
Great! Problem solved!
太棒了，问题解决
On the south route, there's a chicken that plays tic-tac-toe.
但是走南线的话 可以看会玩井字游戏的鸡
Well, back to square one.
又回到原点了
I know a way that you can decide.
我知道有个方法能让你做决定
I'll ask you a series of questions and you answer as quickly as you can.
我会问你一连串的问题 你回答得越快越好
Yes!
好！
Good. But wait.
很好，不过先别急
Here we go. I want you to relax.
开始罗，你先放轻松
Take a deep breath.
深呼吸一口气
Clear your mind.
心里不要想事情
-Peanut butter or egg whites? -Peanut butter.
花生酱和蛋白，你喜欢哪个？ 花生酱
-Be a fireman or a swimmer? -Swimmer.
你比较想当消防员还是游泳选手? 游泳选手
-You'd sleep with Monica or Rachel? -Monica.
摩妮卡和瑞秋 你比较想跟谁上床？ 摩妮卡…
I always thought it'd be Rachel.
我一直都以为会是瑞秋呢
-No thinking. Tie or ascot? -Ascot.
不要想事情… 领带或领巾？ 领巾
-North or south route? -North.
南线或北线？ 北线
Bam! There you go! Huh?
答案出现，厉害吧
That was incredible! Beard of bees here I come!
不可思议 蜜蜂胡，我来罗
This guy again.
这砘镉掷戳
Hey,what's up?
你好吗？
Not much. Wanna see a movie tonight?
普通，今晚想看电影吗？
What do you wanna see?
好啊，你要看什么？
I don't know.
不知道…
I know how to decide. Show him your game.
我知道我们要如何决定 菲比，让他见识你的游戏
No, thank you.
免了，多谢
What's with her?
她是怎么了？
I don't know. I know how we can decide.
不知道，但我知道怎么决定了
I'm gonna ask you questions and you answer real quick.
我问你问题，你要很快回答 好
-Action or comedy? -Action.
动作片或喜剧 你比较喜欢哪一个？ 动作片
Who would you rather sleep with, Monica or Rachel?
摩妮卡和瑞秋 你比较想跟谁上床？
Dude, you are sick.
老兄，你真变态
I'm sorry. I forgot you had that whole Rachel thing.
抱歉，我忘了你迷恋过瑞秋
Oh, my God. What does that thing do?
天啊，这是干嘛的？
-An eye removal machine. -I'm out of here.
这是眼球摘除机 好了，我要走了
I'm kidding.
开玩笑的啦…
Rachel,I'm Dr. Miller.
瑞秋，我是米勒医生
Monica said you were nervous. Everything will be fine.
摩妮卡说你有点紧张 不过别担心，不会有事的
-So we're done. -Almost, but first we gotta start.
那就结束吧 快了，不过我们要先开始
This is a glaucoma test. Sit down.
这是青光眼测试 请坐
Put your chin here.
把脸颊放在这里
Now, you'll feel a small puff of air in each eye.
好，眼睛会有风吹的感觉
What?
什么？
A small puff of air. Now, come on!
一点点的风啦，你快点！
Here we go.
来罗 好
One,two,three.
一、二、三…
I'm sorry. All right.
抱歉…好吧
I'm gonna stay in here this time.
我这次不会动
Ready?
好了吗？
-One,two -I'm sorry.
一、二… 抱歉
You know what? I'm gonna hold her head.
我来抓她头好了
That's okay.
好
一、二…
I'm sorry.
对不起
You're young. You don't have glaucoma.
你还年轻，应该没有青光眼
So it was very, very nice to meet you, sir.
太好了，很高兴认识您
What are you? Are you crazy?
你在干嘛？你疯了不成？
You got a small, minor infection in that left eye.
好，你的左眼有些微感染
Take these drops for a week and you'll be as good as new.
这眼药水一天点三次 连续一周你就宛如新生了
No, I don't put things in my eye.
我不把任何东西放进眼睛里
We'll see you here in three months. And I'll fit you for a glass eye.
那好吧，三个月后再见 太棒了 我到时帮你装上义眼
Give me the damn drops!
好啦，把那死眼药水给我
Dr. Miller?
米勒医生？
P-E-C-F-D.
P、E、C、F、D
Very good, Monica!
摩妮卡，棒极了
-You know where they are. -I sure do.
你知道奖品放在哪里 我当然知道
And you don't get one.
你没有！
You know,those eye drops are a miracle.
那眼药水实在是太神奇了
My eye is 100 percent better.
我的眼睛百分之百好了
-They're still in my coat. -Damn!
眼药水还放在我的外套里 可恶
-You ready to go? -Yeah.
准备好上路了没？  好了
How cold will it be there? Will all these sweater vests be enough?
不过那边会有多冷？ 我要带外套 还是带这些毛衣就够了？
-What? -I love you.
怎么了？ 我爱你
I wish Ross was coming with us. I'll miss him.
真希望罗斯也能一起去 我一定会很想念他的
Thanks. I just got that jerk out of my mind.
真是多谢你了 我才刚把那个混蛋给忘掉
Is the movie putting us up in a big hotel suite?
我们住哪里？ 电影公司招待的饭店大套房？
Not really. It's an independent film.
不算是，这是独立制片的电影
We don't have a big budget. I'll stay in your room.
没有大预算 我想我住你房间好了
Once you get paid, you'll be springing for a suite.
了解，但等你拿到酬劳之后 你会请我住饭店大套房吧？
They must be paying you a lot.
主演电影的片酬一定不少吧？
Yeah. For every dollar Shutterspeed makes...
是啊，我算给你听 “极限速度”每赚一块钱
...one penny of it goes right in Joey's pocket.
乔伊就能分到百分之一
You don't get paid unless it makes money?
所以电影赚钱你才有钱拿？
Did you not hear the plot of the movie?
你不知道这电影的情节吗？
"She's been dead for 10 years."
“贝丝已经过世十年了”
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
我就快变成百万富翁了
I wanted to say goodbye.
我只是要来跟你们说个再见
And to see if you guys would place a little bet for me.
顺便托你们帮我下个注
Twenty bucks on black 15.
20美元押黑色15号
-You got it! -All right.
没问题 好
-You remember the number,right? -Yeah,black 13.
你记得号码吧？ 记得，黑色13号
-Black 15! -You got it.
黑色15号啦! 没问题
-All right. Bye-bye,now. -Bye,you guys.
再见…
I'll say bye at the car.
我去车子那里替你送行
Anyone wanna say bye to me at the car?
谁要去车子那里替我送行？
I'll say goodbye to you at the car if you don't mind the pus.
我可以替你送行 只要你不介意我眼睛化脓
See you!
再见
But wait a minute. The pus is good. It means it's healing.
等等，化脓是好现象 表示快要好了
Hey, Phoebe. What you reading?
菲比，你在看什么？
菲比？
Hello?
菲比？…
Come on!
菲比？别闹了啦
I'm sorry, I didn't see you there.
抱歉，我不知道你在这里
Phoebe, are you mad at me or something?
菲比，你在生我的气吗？
If you are, please tell me what it is I did.
我做了什么让你生气的事？
-lf you don't know, I can't help you. -I don't know.
你不知道，我也帮不了你 我是不知道啊
Well, I can't help you.
那我也无能为力了
Well, whatever it is, I am very, very sorry. Okay?
不管是什么事，我都非常抱歉
Apology accepted.
我接受你的道歉
So we're good?
那我们没事了？
好吧
I'll see you later,okay?
那晚点见罗
Bye,fat-ass.
好，大屁股
All right!
够了！
Will you please tell me what it is that made you so mad at me?
菲比，你快点说 我做了什么让你这么不爽？
I don't know! I don't remember!
我不知道，我不记得了
What do you mean, you can't remember?
什么叫做你不记得了？
I was so focused on being mad at you, I forgot what it was I was mad about.
我太专心在生你的气 气到都忘了生气的原因
If you can't remember, can't we just forget about this?
既然忘了，那能不能就算了？
Oh,no. I am mad at you. I know that much.
不行，我生你的气，这很确定
But I'm sorry about the fat-ass thing because you have a sweet, little heinie.
但我很抱歉骂你大屁股 因为你的小屁屁很可爱
I'm getting pretty tired. You'll have to take over soon.
我开得好累，你随时准备接手
We've been driving for a half-hour. You haven't looked at the road once.
我们才上路半小时 而且你都没在看路
Don't worry. It's out there.
别担心，路就是路嘛
Maybe I just need lunch. You wanna eat?
我想我该吃午饭了 是啊 你要吃吗？
My treat.
我请客
Isn't that Ross' money?
那不是罗斯的钱吗？
Ross' treat. Where do you wanna eat?
是啊，好吧，罗斯请客 你想吃什么？
I don't know.
我不知道
I know how we can decide.
我知道要怎么决定了
I'll ask you questions.
我问你一堆问题
And then you have to answer real fast.
你得很快回答
So clear your mind. Clear it right out. Clear it out.
不要想事情，什么都不要想 好
It's all clear except for this image of a small, purple lamp.
我没在想事情 但心里有个小紫灯的形象
Is that all right if that stays in there?
这样不碍事吧？
I don't see why not. I guess.
应该不碍事吧…
You have to answer with the first thing that pops into your head, okay?
想到什么就直接回答 好
-Would you rather be too wet or too dry? -Too dry.
你宁愿太湿或太干？ 太干
-Do you believe in ghosts? -No.
你相不相信有鬼？ 不相信
-Will this movie be my big break? -No.
这电影会让我翻身吗？ 不会
-What? -Yes.
什么？ 会
-Dude,you said,no. -I also said,yes.
你刚才说不会 我也说了会啊
-This won't be my big break? -No.
你不觉得我这次会翻身？ 对
I don't believe this.
岂有此理
Look, I just don't want you to get your hopes up too high.
乔伊，我只是不要你期望太高
What are you talking about? I'm the lead in a movie!
你在胡说什么？ 我是电影主角耶！
They're not even paying you! This doesn't sound like a real movie!
那他们还不付你片酬？ 这电影听来跟幌子一样
I don't know why you're dumping all over my big break.
我不需要听这种话 搞不懂你干嘛泄我的气
I don't think this is gonna be your big break.
乔伊，我不认为你这次能翻身
Are you on this trip to make me feel like a loser?
所以你才来这趟？ 让我觉得自己是窝囊废？
-I'd rather be alone. -You don't want me here?
如果是这样，那我宁愿自己去
Not if you're like this.
你不要我陪你去？ 你这样我不要也罢
The next time you ask me a question like that,I'll lie.
那好吧，下次你再问那种问题 我骗你就是了
I don't want you on the trip.
对！我不要你一起去
Why don't you pull over. I'll get out now.
好，无所谓… 你停车，我马上走
Fine.
好啊
Get out.
滚吧
You can't stop on a bridge.
在桥上不能随便就停车
-Get out! -Fine!
滚啦！ 好啦！
Wait! Wait! There's no sidewalk!
等等…桥上没有人行道！
Yeah. I'm gonna die here.
我一定会死在这里
“中央咖啡馆”
Are you mad at me because my hair gel smells?
好，你生我的气 是因为我发胶有怪味？
不是
Because I said your handwriting is childlike?
你生我的气 是因为我说你写字像小孩？
No. That made me feel precious.
不是，这样才特别啊
Because he's always correcting people's grammar?
我知道了 因为他老爱纠正别人文法？
"Whom, whom." Sometimes it's "who"!
什么“WHOM”个没完 有时候是用“WHO”啦！
Yeah? Sometimes it's:
是吗？有时候是…
Did you beat him at a board game? He's such a baby when he loses.
还是你玩西洋棋赢了他？ 他开始居于劣势就很孩子气
Okay, I'm the baby.
好，我孩子气
Hey! Stop it!
住手！
What are you doing here?
钱德，你怎么会在这里？
Joey kicked me out of the car on the bridge.
乔伊在华盛顿大桥上 把我赶下车
-Why? -I don't know. He went crazy.
为什么？… 不知道，他突然发飙
We played that game where you ask questions and answer fast.
我们在玩快问快答的游戏
That game should not be played without my supervision.
没有我在场监督 绝对不能玩那个游戏
I don't know what made him mad.
我不知道他干嘛气成那样
All I said was that this wouldn't be his big break...
我只是说他这次不会翻身
...that it wouldn't do anything for him...
说这部电影帮不了他
...and that it didn't sound real.
说这部电影很像是幌子
Okay, he should've pushed me off the bridge.
好啦，他该把我推下桥才对
What's in the bag?
你袋子里有什么？
I figured you'd be mad at me...
我猜想你们大家也会对我不爽
...so I got gifts that I found on the roadside.
所以我在路边检了些礼物
-Who wants the one-legged teddy bear? -I do!
谁要一条腿的泰迪熊？ 我要
来了
-Not even close. -I need help! I can't do this.
差远了 好啦，你帮我，我没办法
Come on. Let's do it.
来，我帮你
Sit down. All right, put your head back.
坐下 好 头往后仰 好
-Now open your eyes. -Okay,they are.
把眼睛张开 好，张开了
-How many fingers am I holding up? -Four.
我举了几只手指头？ 四只
I was thinking four.
天啊，我心里想的也是四只
-Really? -Yes!
真的？ 是啊
Why don't we start with a practice one.
这样吧，我们先来预演一次 好
-No drops. -Great!
不滴眼药水 太好了
On three. One,two,three.
数到三，一、二、三…
My pillow's all wet!
你害我沙发枕都湿了
Well,you said it was practice!
你自己说是预演的
Why did you move?
那你干嘛动？
I knew you were lying!
因为我知道你在骗我
-Come here. -What are you doing?
好吧，过来 你要干嘛？
Stop it! Oh,my God!
摩妮卡，天啊！住手！…
I am going....
我要…
Turn it over!
转回来！
I am going to get...
我要把...
...get these drops in your eye.
把眼药水…滴进你眼睛
Oh, my God! You really are freakishly strong.
天啊，你蛮力真大
Stop! Stop!
摩妮卡，住手！…
Stop it!
住手
Damn,it's empty!
可恶，滴完了！
If Joey and Chandler walked in now, we could make a fortune.
如果现在乔伊和钱德走进来 我们就发了
That is definitely Chandler, Joey or Ross.
一定是钱德、乔伊或罗斯
Or Rachel.
或是瑞秋
It's Joey.
喂？ 是乔伊
Chandler told me what happened. He's really upset.
真高兴你打来 钱德都说了，他很难过
Not as upset as he'll be when he finds out what I did with his sweater vests.
等他知道他毛衣的下场 他一定会更难过
What did you do to them?
你把他的毛衣怎么了？
There's a well-dressed pack of dogs in Ohio.
这么说吧，在俄亥俄州 有一伙打扮亮丽的狗
I gotta ask Phoebe something about the car.
摩妮卡？菲比在吗？ 我有车子的事要问她
Hold on one second.
她在，你等等
-Hey, dude. -Hey, Phoebe.
嗨 嗨，菲比，你听我说
This wooden box keeps sliding out. What is it?
座位底下有个木盒滑出来 那是什么？
My grandma.
那是我祖母
And thanks. She's having a great time.
乔伊，谢谢你，她玩得很愉快
Is that Joey? Let me talk to him.
是乔伊吗？我要跟他说…
Chandler's here. He was wondering if
乔伊？钱德不知道你…
I guess he ran out of change.
我想他零钱正好用完了
How am I gonna apologize to him if he won't even talk to me?
他连话都不想跟我说 这样我要怎么跟他道歉？
Send him something. So when he gets there, he'll know you're sorry.
或许你应该寄点东西给他 等他到了赌城 就知道你想表达歉意了
That's a good idea. I wonder where I could get a basket of porn?
好主意，上哪儿找一堆A片？
No,don't say, "I'm sorry," with porn.
不行，不能用A片道歉啦 真的？
You should send him a carton of cigarettes.
你应该寄一条烟过去
Because that way he can trade it for protection.
他可以用来换取保护
No. That's prison.
错了，监狱里才是这样
I know how we're gonna figure this out.
菲比，我知道要怎么找出原因
Clear your mind...
好，什么都不要想
...and answer the first thing that comes into your head.
想到什么就直接回答
-Do you like flora or fauna? -Fauna.
你比较喜欢植物还是动物？ 动物
-Simon or Garfunkel? -Garfunkel.
你想当赛门还是葛芬柯？ 葛芬柯
-Why are you mad? -You said I was boring.
你为何生我的气？ 因为你说我很无趣
When did I say that?
我何时说过你无趣了？
Oh,my God! I remember now! We were playing chess.
天啊，我想起来了 我们下西洋棋那次
Phoebe,you and l have never played chess.
菲比，我和你没下过西洋棋
Remember that time on the frozen lake? We were playing. You said I was boring.
有啦，记得冰冻湖那次吗？ 我们玩西洋棋，你说我很无趣
Then you took off your energy mask and you were Cameron Diaz.
然后你脱下面具 变成了卡麦蓉狄亚
There's a chance this may have been a dream.
好吧，这有可能是梦境
So this entire time,you've been angry with me because of a dream?
所以你这阵子以来对我不爽 全是因为一场梦？
Well, guess what, now I'm mad at you.
菲比，现在轮我不爽你了
I wanted to make sure this wasn't a dream.
我想确定这次不是作梦
Otherwise we're wasting our time.
免得浪费彼此的时间
Stanley!
史丹利！
Your leading man is here. Let's get to work.
你的主角来了，咱们开工吧
Slight change of plans.
计划有些改变
We've shut down.
我们停拍了
What? Why?
什么？为什么？
It's a money thing. We don't have any.
我们没钱
You're kidding, right?
你在开玩笑吧？ 不是
What?
什么？
It's probably just temporary.
这或许只是暂时的
We're hoping to get some money soon. Just hang out.
我们希望能快点筹到资金 你先撑一下
Hang out? How long?
撑一下？要撑多久？
I don't know. A week. Maybe two. The money will turn up.
不知道，一、两个星期吧 资金会出现的
People always wanna invest in movies. You're not rich?
大家都爱投资拍电影 你该不会是有钱人吧？ 我不是
Worth a shot.
问一下也无妨
Well, Joey, let me know where you're staying,okay?
乔伊，让我知道你在哪儿落脚
Hey, pal. Are you Joey Tribbiani?
你是乔伊崔比亚尼吗？ 我是
These got left for you.
这是有人留给你的
Thanks.
谢了
"Congratulations on your big break."
恭喜你翻身了
-Monica, it's Joey. -Hey,Joey.
喂？ 摩妮卡，我是乔伊
You remember me even though you're a star.
你当了大明星还是记得我
Come on. It'll be years before I forget you.
得了吧，忘记你也要好几年
What's it like on a movie set?
拍片现场是什么样子？
Do you have a dressing room and a chair with your name?
你有自己的更衣室吗？ 有专属的私人座椅吗？
Yeah,yeah,I got all that going on.
有啊，一切都在进行当中
Tell Chandler he couldn't have been more wrong.
你一定要跟钱德说 他完完全全看走眼了
I gotta go,Monica. My sushi's here.
摩妮卡，我得挂了 我的寿司送来了
Sorry about that. Thanks for waiting.
抱歉，多谢你们等我 没关系
Everybody smile.
大家笑一个，多谢
Thanks a lot. Enjoy your stay at Caesars. We hope it's toga-rific.
希望你们在凯萨住得愉快 祝福你们“罗马”精神
Kill me. Kill me now.
杀了我吧…
Rach, can you pass me the TV Guide?
瑞秋，电视指南递给我好吗？ 好啊
Go!
上！
What are you doing? Get off! Oh, my God!
住手！…天啊！
Hold it open. Okay.
好了…
We'll see you in about three or four hours.
三、四个小时后再见